Register to The Benny Goodman Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Band and Combo Arrangements
  - GOODBYE (Box 10A, Folder 20)
    Score includes added parts by Eddie Sauter c.1945.
  - GOODBYE Burns, Ralph (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - GOODBYE (Box 10B, Folder 20A)
    BG No.: "last"
  - GOODMAN IS HARD TO FIND, A Jenkins, Gordon, 4-5/1976 (Box 10B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: G143
    Includes part for conductor. Complete.
  - GOODMAN ON THE GRIDIRON, 1939 (Box 10B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: C145
  - GOODMORNING STAR SHINE Ogerman, Claus (Box 10B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: G1
    Parts: cl(5)/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-4/P(2)G(2)B(2)D
  - GOODNIGHT MY LOVE/GOODNIGHT MY LOVE "REVISED" Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 10B, Folder 24)
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn-3/PGBD
    Full set of parts for "revised" version included.
  - GOODY GOODBYE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 10C, Folder 25)
    BG No.: A27
  - GOODY GOODY (Box 10C, Folder 26)
    BG No.: A341/G2
    Transcription with added PARTS
  - GOODY GOODY Rawitz, Steve, 1978 (Box 10C, Folder 27)
    BG No.: G134
  - GOTTA BE THIS OR THAT (Box 10C, Folder 28)
  - GOTTA BE THIS OR THAT Sampson, Edgar, 1945 (Box 10C, Folder 29)
    BG No.: A135/20A
    Score and parts for "last two choruses" only. Complete.
  - GOTTA BE THIS OR THAT Sampson, Edgar, 1945 (Box 10C, Folder 30)
    BG No.: A135
    Parts: cl/saxAATTb/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/PGBD
    Includes "last 2 choruses" (BG no.A135).
  - GOTTA BE THIS OR THAT Sampson, Edgar, 1945 (Box 10C, Folder 31)
    BG No.: 261/20/Al 35
    Original score and parts. Complete.
  - GOTTA BE THIS OR THAT Burns, Ralph (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - GOTTA GET SOME SHUT-EYE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 10C, Folder 32)
    BG No.: A68
  - GUESS I'LL GO BACK HOME Mundy, Jimmy, 1939 (Box 10C, Folder 33)
    BG No.: A169/143
  - GUESS WHO Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 01)
    BG No.: B354
  - HALLELUJAH Clayton, Buck, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 02)
    BG No.: B225
    Parts: horn
  - HALLELUJAH Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 03)
    BG No.: 143/71-13
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1,3/PGB
    Parts in Henderson's own hand. Tbn3 added in 1939.
  - HALLELUJAH (Box 11, Folder 04)
    BG No.: C362/57
    Parts: saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/GBD
  - HALLELUJAH I LOVE HER SO Wilson, Gerald, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 05)
    BG No.: F124
  - HANDFUL OF KEYS Burns, Ralph, 5/1963 (Box 11, Folder 06)
    BG No.: F31/10
    Parts: cl/tpt/PBDV/fl
  - HANDFUL OF KEYS Wilcox, Larry, 3/1961 (Box 11, Folder 07)
    BG No.: F31
  - HANDFUL OF KEYS Wilcox, Larry, 5/1963 (Box 11A, Folder 08)
    BG No.: F31/10A
    Parts: cl/tpt/tbn/PBD/fl
  - HANDFUL OF KEYS, 1960 (Box 11A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: G129
  - HAPPY SESSION BLUES, THE Gutesha, Bobby, 1958 (Box 11A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: D49/241
  - HATE TO TALK ABOUT MYSELF Murphy, Spud, 1935 (Box 11A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: C152/36
  - HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN SO SOON Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 11A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: A18/452
  - HAWAIIAN WAR CHANT Stegmeyer, Bill, 10/1960 (Box 11A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: D337/62
  - HE AIN'T GOT RHYTHM Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 11A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: A178/368
  - HE'S A GOOD MAN McGuffie, Bill, 1969 (Box 11B, Folder 15)
    BG No.: G17/H1
    Includes set of parts for 3 tbn version. Complete.
  - HE'S MY GUY Thompson, Johnny, 1942 (Box 11B, Folder 16)
    BG No.: C211/ 97A
    Parts: cl/saxB/tpt1/PGBD
  - HEADS OR TAILS Karlin, Fred, 10/13/1959 (Box 11B, Folder 17)
    BG No.: D61/8
  - HERE'S LOVE IN YOUR EYES Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 11B, Folder 18)
    BG No.: A179/136/268
  - HERE'S THAT RAINY DAY (Box 11B, Folder 19)
    Parts: "rhythm" (3)
  - HIGH-FALUTIN', 1947 (Box 11B, Folder 20)
    BG No.: 102
    Parts: PGB "vibraharp"
  - HONEYSUCKLE ROSE, 1959 (Box 11B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: D226/16
  - HOOSIER SWEETHEART Diaz, Horace, 1934 (Box 11B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: A175/102/683
  - HORA STACCATO Powell, Mel, 1946 (Box 11B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: C234
    Parts: cl1-2/eng horn/bsn1-2/tpt1-2/tbn1-3/D/hp
  - HOT FOOT SHUFFLE Norman, Fred, 1938 (Box 11C, Folder 24)
    BG No.: C207/230
    Parts: cl/saxT(-T2)/tbn1/D
  - HOUR OF PARTING Sauter, Eddie, 1940 (Box 11C, Folder 25)
    BG No.: A136/227/109
    Score: full score and sketch
    Parts: saxAT(-A1T1)/tpt1-3(3)/tbn1,3/BD
  - HOUSE HOP Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 11C, Folder 26)
    BG No.: C206/224
    Parts: cl/saxAAT/tpt1,3/tbn1-3/G
    SaxT and tpt1 parts are incomplete. Parts in Mundy's own hand.
  - HOW ABOUT YOU Carisi, Johnny, 1962 (Box 11C, Folder 27)
    BG No.: D425/294
  - HOW CAN I FORGET Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 11C, Folder 28)
    BG No.: B143
  - HOW DEEP IS THE OCEAN (Box 11C, Folder 29)
    BG No.: 7A
  - HOW HIGH THE MOON Sauter, Eddie, 1940 (Box 11C, Folder 30)
    BG No.: A113
  - HOW HIGH THE MOON Henderson, Fletcher, 1947 (Box 11C, Folder 31)
  - HOW LONG HAS THIS BEEN GOING ON Powell, Mel, 1941 (Box 11C, Folder 32)
    BG No.: A9/42
    Includes score for added parts (tpt4/tbn3), and score for alternate middle section (B2 to 5 measures before E).
  - HOW SWEET YOU ARE Sauter, Eddie, c.1941 (Box 11D, Folder 33)
    BG No.: C336/20
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PBD
    Saxes double flute or clarinet.
  - HOWD'JA LIKE TO LOVE ME Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 11D, Folder 34)
    BG No.: C158
  - HUIDA, LA (Box 11D, Folder 35)
    BG No.: L3
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1,3/tbn1-3/PG(2)BD
  - HUMORESQUE Henderson, Fletcher, 1941 (Box 11D, Folder 36)
    BG No.: B101/34A
    Parts: cl/saxAATIB/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
  - HUNDRED YEARS FROM TODAY, A Schutt, Arthur, 11/1933 (Box 11D, Folder 37)
    BG No.: B350/106
    Vocal arrangement for Ethel Waters.
  - HUNKADOLA Kincaide, Deane, 1935 (Box 11D, Folder 38)
    BG No.: A184
    Parts from a later recopy.
  - HUNKADOLA Kincaide, Deane (Box 11D, Folder 38A)
    BG No.: 40
  - I BELIEVE IN YOU Wilcox, Larry, 5/1963 (Box 11D, Folder 39)
    BG No.: F38
    Parts: cl/saxT/tpt/tbn/PBD
  - I CAN PULL A RABBIT OUT OF MY HAT Murphy, Spud, 1935 (Box 11E, Folder 40)
    BG No.: A315
  - I CAN'T BELIEVE Matz, Peter, 6/1960 (Box 11E, Folder 41)
    BG No.: D315/408
  - I CAN'T GET STARTED Reidy, Frank, 1969 (Box 11E, Folder 42)
    BG No.: G20
    Tpt1 marked "solo"; tpt3-4 marked "tacet". Complete.
  - I CAN'T GET STARTED Lipman, Joe, 9/1961 (Box 11E, Folder 43)
    BG No.: D407/254
  - I CAN'T GET STARTED Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 11E, Folder 44)
    BG No.: A121
  - I CAN'T LOVE YOU ANYMORE Henderson, Fletcher, 1940 (Box 11E, Folder 45)
    BG No.: 308/A39
  - I CRIED FOR YOU Mundy, Jimmy, 1939 (Box 11E, Folder 46)
    BG No.: D34
  - I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TIME IT WAS Nelson, Oliver, 1962 (Box 11E, Folder 47)
    BG No.: D421/282
  - I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TIME IT WAS Karlin, Fred, 5/16/1960 (Box 11E, Folder 48)
    BG No.: D305/38
    Key: E minor
  - I DON'T WANT TO MAKE HISTORY Woode, Henri, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 01)
    BG No.: A316/19
  - I DON'T WANT TO WALK (Box 12, Folder 02)
    BG No.: C353/48A
  - I FEEL A SONG COMING ON Murphy, Spud, 8/3/1935 (Box 12, Folder 03)
    BG No.: A342/54/C349
  - I FEEL A SONG COMING ON, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 04)
    BG No.: C349/54
    Parts: cl/saxAAT(-T2)/tpt1-3/tbn2/PGBD
  - I FOUND A DREAM Murphy, Spud, 11/10/1935 (Box 12, Folder 05)
    BG No.: A317/10
  - I FOUND A NEW BABY Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 06)
    BG No.: 137/172/C348
    Parts: cl/saxA(2)A(2)T(2)TB/tpt1-3/tbn1(2)-3(2)/PGBD
    Includes newly copied PARTS
  - I FOUND A NEW BABY Hensel, Wes, 3/1961 (Box 12, Folder 07)
    BG No.: A94
  - I FOUND A NEW BABY Stegmeyer, Bill, 1960 (Box 12A, Folder 08)
    BG No.: D343/69
  - I GET A KICK OUT OF YOU Gutesha, Bobby, 1958 (Box 12A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: D65/254
  - I GO FOR THAT Norman, Fred, 11/1938 (Box 12A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: A318/14
  - I GOT A GAL IN KALAMAZOO Powell, Mel, 1941 (Box 12A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: A185/34A
    Parts: saxB/tpt1/PGB
  - I GOT RHYTHM Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 12A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: C273
    Parts: cl/saxAAT(-T2)/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PBD
  - I GOTTA RIGHT TO SING THE BLUES Brookmeyer, Bob, 5/1962 (Box 12A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: D411/296
  - I GOTTA RIGHT TO SING THE BLUES, 1/1959 (Box 12A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: D411
    Parts: c1/saxT/tbn/PGBD
  - I HAD TO DO IT Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 12A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: A17/767
  - I HAPPEN TO BE IN LOVE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 12B, Folder 16)
    BG No.: B1 45/D2/271
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/GBD
  - I HATE TO LOSE YOU Henderson, Fletcher, 1947 (Box 12B, Folder 17)
    BG No.: B234
  - I HATE YOU DARLING Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 12B, Folder 18)
    BG No.: B348
  - I HAVE EYES Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 12B, Folder 19)
    BG No.: A38/56
  - I HAVEN'T TIME TO BE A MILLIONAIRE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 12B, Folder 20)
  - I HEAR A CALL TO ARMS Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 12B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: A319
  - I HEAR BLUEBIRDS Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 12B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: A30
    Photocopy of score missing finale page (pg.11).
  - I JUST COULDN'T TAKE IT BABY Schutt, Arthur, 1933 (Box 12B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: A156/91
  - I KISS YOUR HAND MADAME Sauter, Eddie (Box 12B, Folder 24)
    BG No.: B146
    All parts photocopies. Complete.
  - I KNOW THAT YOU KNOW Henderson, Fletcher, 1936 (Box 12B, Folder 25)
    BG No.: C347/176
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-2/tbn1/PG(2)D
    SaxB and extra guitar part are from a later recopy.
  - I KNOW THAT YOU KNOW Lipman, Joe, 8/1962 (Box 12C, Folder 26)
    BG No.: F8
  - I KNOW THAT YOU KNOW (Box 12C, Folder 26A)
    BG No.: F8/Il/97A/28
  - I LET A SONG GO OUT OF MY HEART Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 12C, Folder 27)
    Score: last page only
  - I LET A SONG GO OUT OF MY HEART Williams, George, 1958 (Box 12C, Folder 28)
    BG No.: B379/245
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD/voca1
  - I LOVE SWING Henderson, Horace, c.1939 (Box 12C, Folder 29)
    BG No.: A320
  - I LOVE TO WHISTLE Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 12C, Folder 30)
    BG No.: A260/23
  - I MAY BE WRONG Potts, Bill, 4/16/1959 (Box 12D, Folder 31)
    BG No.: B147
  - I MAY BE WRONG Karlin, Fred, 4/25/1960 (Box 12D, Folder 32)
    BG No.: D302/34
  - I MAY BE WRONG Jenkins, Gordon, 5/1976 (Box 12D, Folder 33)
    BG No.: G140
    These parts are photocopies: cl/saxT2/tpt2-4/GB. Complete.
  - I MAY BE WRONG Pleis, Jack, 1946 (Box 12D, Folder 34)
  - I MUST HAVE THAT MAN Hensel, Wes, 2/1961 (Box 12D, Folder 35)
    BG No.: A14
  - I MUST SEE ANNIE TONIGHT Norman, Fred, 1938 (Box 12D, Folder 36)
    BG No.: B113/8
  - I NEVER KNEW I COULD LOVE ANYBODY Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 12D, Folder 37)
    BG No.: A122/4A
  - I ONLY HAVE EYES FOR YOU (Box 12D, Folder 38)
    Parts: rhythm part (3)
  - I ONLY HAVE EYES FOR YOU Gutesha, Bobby, 1958 (Box 12E, Folder 39)
    BG No.: D66/255
  - I SEE A MILLION PEOPLE Sauter, Eddie, 9/13/1941 (Box 12E, Folder 40)
    BG No.: B148
  - I THOUGHT ABOUT YOU Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 12E, Folder 41)
    BG No.: A105
    Parts from 1947 recopy. Complete.
  - I THOUGHT ABOUT YOU Boland, Francis, c.1956 (Box 12E, Folder 42)
    BG No.: D410
    Vocal arrangement for Martha Tilton. Complete.
  - I TOLD MY HEART Sauter, Eddie, 1945 (Box 12E, Folder 43)
    BG No.: B346
  - I WALK WITH YOU Newsom, Tommy, 10/20/1965 (Box 12E, Folder 44)
    BG No.: F114
  - I WANNA BE LOVED Stein, Ralph, 1946 (Box 12E, Folder 45)
    BG No.: C257/95A/A106
    Includes piano/vocal sheet music. Last page of clarinet part is missing.
  - I WANT A NEW ROMANCE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 12E, Folder 46)
    BG No.: B347/8
  - I WANT MY SHARE OF LOVE Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 01)
    BG No.: B332
  - I WANT TO BE HAPPY Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 02)
    BG No.: B149
  - I WANT TO BE HAPPY Stegmeyer, Bill, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 03)
    BG No.: D345/20A/15
    Parts: cl/saxA/tpt/tbn/PGBDV
  - I WANT TO BE HAPPY Cohn, Al, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 04)
    BG No.: D78/20
    Score: yes (original inst.: w/o saxA/tpt/V)
    Arrangement includes added parts (saxA/tpt/V), and paste-over changes to original inst. to fit expanded version. Complete.
  - I WANT TO BE HAPPY Clayton, Buck, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 05)
    BG No.: B149/27
    Parts: cl/saxAATB(-T2)/tpt1-4/tbn1-2/PGBD/horn
  - I WANT YOU Edwards, Teddy (Box 13, Folder 06)
    BG No.: F129
    Parts: cl/saxTB/tpt1-2/tbn/PGBD/choir(4)
    Includes extra score for vocal parts. Complete.
  - I WAS DOING ALRIGHT Mundy, Jimmy, 1938 (Box 13A, Folder 07)
    BG No.: A262/93
  - I WAS LUCKY Murphy, Spud, 1934 (Box 13A, Folder 08)
    BG No.: C332/34
  - I WILL WAIT FOR YOU Knight, Peter, 1970 (Box 13A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: G102/I2
  - I WISH I COULD TELL YOU, 1945 (Box 13A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: C328/87A
  - I WISH I HAD YOU Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 13A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: A21
  - I WISHED UPON A STAR (Box 13A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: C110/309
  - I WON'T DANCE Schutt, Arthur, 1936 (Box 13A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: A26 3/ 100
    Vocal arrangement for Helen Ward and chorus.
  - I WON'T DANCE Diaz Jr., Horace (Box 13A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: 142
  - I WON'T SNAP Karlin, Fred, 5/31/1960 (Box 13A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: D308/44
  - I WOULD DO ANYTHING FOR YOU Burns, Ralph, 5/1963 (Box 13A, Folder 16)
    BG No.: F33/8
  - I WOULD DO MOST ANYTHING FOR YOU (Box 13B, Folder 17)
    BG No.: B339/230
  - I WOULD DO MOST ANYTHING FOR YOU Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 13B, Folder 18)
    BG No.: A333/40
  - I WOULD DO MOST ANYTHING FOR YOU Henderson, Fletcher (Box 13B, Folder 17A)
    BG No.: A7/4
  - I'D DO IT AGAIN Thompson, Johnny, 1942 (Box 13B, Folder 19)
    BG No.: C201/ 91 A
    Parts: cl/saxB/tPt3/PGBD
  - I'D LIKE TO SEE SAMOA OF SAMOA Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 13B, Folder 20)
    BG No.: A391
  - I'D RATHER LEAD A BAND Burns, Ralph (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - I'LL DREAM TONIGHT Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 13B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: A286/36
  - I'LL GET BY Wilder, Alec, c.1940 (Box 13B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: 31
  - I'LL NEVER SMILE AGAIN Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 13B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: B151
  - I'M ALL SMILES Napp, Ken (Box 13B, Folder 24)
    BG No.: G118/A4
  - I'M ALWAYS CHASING RAINBOWS Sauter, Eddie, 1940 (Box 13B, Folder 25)
    BG No.: A124/202E
  - I'M AN OLD COWHAND Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 13B, Folder 26)
    BG No.: B328/121
  - I'M BUBBLING OVER Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 13C, Folder 27)
    BG No.: A167/440
  - I'M BUILDING UP TO AN AWFUL LETDOWN Woode, Henri, 1936 (Box 13C, Folder 28)
    BG No.: A162
  - I'M COMING VIRGINIA Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 13C, Folder 29)
    BG No.: A144/283
  - I'M CONFESSIN' THAT I LOVE YOU Caligan, Woody, 1945 (Box 13C, Folder 30)
    BG No.: 24A
  - I'M FEELIN' LIKE A MILLION Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 13C, Folder 31)
    BG No.: A163/285
  - I'M GLAD THERE IS YOU Bunch, John, 1962 (Box 13C, Folder 32)
    BG No.: F3/278
  - I'M GONNA SIT RIGHT DOWN Henderson, Fletcher, 1946 (Box 13C, Folder 33)
    BG No.: A331/I5
  - I'M GONNA SIT RIGHT DOWN Henderson, Fletcher, 1946 (Box 13C, Folder 34)
    BG No.: C214/5A
    Parts: cl/saxAT(-A2T2)/tpt1-2/tbn1-2/PGB
  - I'M HAPPY DARLING, DANCING WITH YOU Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 13D, Folder 35)
    BG No.: A328/16
  - I'M IN A CRYING MOOD Henderson, Fletcher, 1946 (Box 13D, Folder 36)
    BG No.: 111
    Parts: PGBD
  - I'M JUST LIKE A FISH OUT OF WATER Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 13D, Folder 37)
    BG No.: A329/77
  - I'M JUST WILD ABOUT HARRY Sauter, Eddie, 1943 (Box 13D, Folder 38)
    BG No.: B229/105
    Parts: cl/saxAATTBBs/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/PGBD
    Bass sax part not indicated in score and numbered 32A. Horn in F can substitute for tbn3. Complete.
  - I'M MADLY IN LOVE WITH YOU Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 13D, Folder 39)
    BG No.: A330
  - I'M MAKIN' BELIEVE Sauter, Eddie, 1944 (Box 13D, Folder 40)
    BG No.: A126
    Written for the movie "Sweet and Lowdown".
  - I'M NOT COMPLAININ' Sampson, Edgar, 1941 (Box 13D, Folder 41)
    BG No.: B176
    Score: incomplete; final page(s) missing
  - I'M STEPPIN' OUT WITH A MEMORY TONIGHT Brooks, Dudley, 1940 (Box 13D, Folder 42)
    BG No.: B153
  - I'M TALKING THROUGH MY HEART Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 13E, Folder 43)
    BG No.: A378/21 0
  - I'M THRILLED Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 13E, Folder 44)
    BG No.: B154
  - I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 13E, Folder 45)
    BG No.: B250
  - I'VE GOT A BLUE EYED BLOND Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 13E, Folder 46)
    BG No.: A209
  - I'VE GOT A CRUSH ON YOU Thompson, Johnny, 1943 (Box 13E, Folder 47)
    BG No.: C373/16
    Parts: saxAATTBs/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
  - I'VE GOT A CRUSH ON YOU Massingill, O.B. (Box 13E, Folder 48)
  - I'VE GOT A FEELING I'M FALLING Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 13E, Folder 49)
    BG No.: A108/59
  - I'VE GOT A HEAVY DATE Henderson, Fletcher, 1936 (Box 13E, Folder 50)
    BG No.: A54/43/491
  - I'VE GOT FIVE DOLLARS Diaz, Horace, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 01)
    BG No.: B79/98
  - I'VE GOT MY LOVE TO KEEP ME WARM Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 02)
    Parts: cl/saxA(-A2)/tpt1-2/tbn1/PGD
  - I'VE GOT MY LOVE TO KEEP ME WARM Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 03)
    BG No.: A109
  - I'VE GOT YOU UNDER MY SKIN Gutesha, Bobby, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 04)
    BG No.: D63/252
  - I'VE HAD MY MOMENTS Baranco, Wilbert (Box 14, Folder 05)
    BG No.: C372
    Parts: saxATT(-A1)/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/PGBDV
  - IDAHO Kirkpatrick, Don, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 06)
    BG No.: C202/84A
  - IDAHO (POTATOES) (Box 14, Folder 07)
    BG No.: A114
  - IF I COULD BE WITH YOU (Box 14, Folder 7A)
    BG No.: D41/I3/11
  - IF I HAD YOU Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 08)
    BG No.: A10/C258/99
  - IF I HAD YOU White, Johnny, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 09)
    BG No.: B224
  - IF I HAD YOU (Box 14A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: B224/34A
  - IF I'M LUCKY, 1946 (Box 14A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: B392
  - IF IT'S GOOD Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 14A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: C1 13/151
    Key: k flat
  - IF IT'S LOVE Schutt, Arthur, 1934 (Box 14A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: B251/71
  - IF IT'S TRUE Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 14A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: B150/C379/17A
    Parts: cl/saxAATB(-T2)/tpt1-3/tbn1/PGBD
  - IF THE MOON TURNS GREEN Murphy, Spud, 2/27/1935 (Box 14A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: A168/118
  - IF WE NEVER MEET AGAIN Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 14A, Folder 16)
    BG No.: A334/173
  - IF YOU BUILD A BETTER MOUSETRAP Sauter, Eddie (Box 14A, Folder 17)
    BG No.: A252/607
  - IF YOU EVER CHANGE YOUR MIND Mundy, Jimmy, 1939 (Box 14A, Folder 18)
    BG No.: B326/127/188
  - IF YOU LOVE ME Murphy, Spud, 1935 (Box 14A, Folder 19)
    BG No.: A285/86
  - IF YOU PLEASE Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 14A, Folder 20)
    BG No.: B327
  - IF YOU PLEASE Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 14A, Folder 21)
  - ILL WIND Stegmeyer, Bill, 6-7/1960 (Box 14B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: D325/53
  - IMAGE OF YOU, THE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 14B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: A387/7
  - IMAGINATION (Box 14B, Folder 24)
    BG No.: B152
    Parts: saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PBD
  - IMPRESSIONS Appleyard, Peter (Box 14B, Folder 25)
    Score: none
    Parts: PBD
  - IN A MELLOW TONE Nelson, Oliver, 4/1962 (Box 14B, Folder 26)
    BG No.: D422/274
  - IN A MOMENT OF WEAKNESS Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 14B, Folder 27)
    BG No.: A325
  - IN THE MOOD Henderson, Fletcher, 1940 (Box 14B, Folder 28)
    BG No.: A46/64/251
  - IN THE SHADE OF THE OLD APPLE TREE Henderson, Fletcher, 1937 (Box 14B, Folder 29)
    BG No.: A344/105E/206/92
    Drum part very recent recopy. Complete.
  - INCOGNITO Clayton, Buck, 1946 (Box 14C, Folder 30)
    BG No.: C136/52
  - INDIAN SUMMER Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 14C, Folder 31)
    BG No.: B207
  - INTERMEZZO Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 14C, Folder 32)
    BG No.: A332/32
  - INVITATION TO A DANCE (Box 14C, Folder 33)
    BG No.: C111/58
  - IT AIN'T RIGHT Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 14C, Folder 34)
    BG No.: B330/107/206
  - IT ALL COMES BACK TO ME NOW Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 14C, Folder 35)
    BG No.: B1 56/53A
    Parts: cl
  - IT DON'T MEAN A THING Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 14C, Folder 36)
    BG No.: A326/62
  - IT HAPPENED IN CHICAGO Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 14C, Folder 37)
    BG No.: A327/155
  - IT LOOKS LIKE RAIN Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 14C, Folder 38)
    BG No.: 116
  - IT NEVER ENTERED MY MIND, 1959 (Box 14C, Folder 39)
    BG No.: C18
    Parts: cl/saxT/tbn/PG("rhythm" and "solo")BD
  - IT WAS A VERY GOOD YEAR Newsom, Tommy, 12/1965 (Box 14C, Folder 40)
    BG No.: F113/I6
    All saxAT parts double clarinet; saxB doubles bass clarinet.; Complete.
  - IT'S A WONDERFUL WORLD Brooks, Dudley, 5/29/1940 (Box 14D, Folder 41)
    BG No.: B157
  - IT'S ALL RIGHT WITH ME Norman, Fred, 2/1956 (Box 14D, Folder 42)
    BG No.: A345/171
    Parts and score mislabeled "It's the Right Time". Complete.
  - IT'S ALL RIGHT WITH ME Stegmeyer, Bill (Box 14D, Folder 43)
    BG No.: D329/41 1
    Score: missing pg.1
  - IT'S ALL RIGHT WITH ME Newsom, Tommy, 5/1963 (Box 14D, Folder 44)
    BG No.: F36/26
  - IT'S ALWAYS YOU Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 14D, Folder 45)
    BG No.: C259/2A
  - IT'S AN OLD SOUTHERN CUSTOM Henderson, Fletcher, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 01)
    BG No.: A368/4
  - IT'S BEEN SO LONG Rose, David, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 02)
    BG No.: B334/31
    Score: yes (no introduction)
    Score and parts from 1953 recopy. Vocal arrangement. Complete.
  - IT'S BEEN SO LONG Powell, Mel, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 03)
    BG No.: D13/B334
    Parts: cl/saxATB/tpt/tbn/PGBDV/fl/horn
  - IT'S BEEN SO LONG (Box 15, Folder 04)
    BG No.: A346/59
    Score: for "new brass" only
    Parts: tpt2-3/tbn1-2
    These parts may be intended to fit with the Mel Powell arrangement.
  - IT'S BEEN SO LONG Rose, David, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 05)
    BG No.: 465B
    Parts: saxAA/tpt1-3/tbn1-2
    These are original parts.
  - IT'S BEEN SO LONG Murphy, Spud, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 06)
    BG No.: A346
    Parts: saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1
    SaxT2 is incomplete.
  - IT'S D'LOVELY Pierce, Nat, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 07)
    BG No.: C281/224
  - IT'S GOOD-MAN, c.1945 (Box 15, Folder 08)
    BG No.: C137/107
  - IT'S NEVER TOO LATE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 15A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: A40/184
  - IT'S RAINING MEMORIES Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 15A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: B158
  - IT'S SO PEACEFUL IN THE COUNTRY Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 15A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: B1 59/303
    This set of parts from a 1962 recopy and expansion. See original score in other arrangement (BG no. B159/97A).
  - IT'S SO PEACEFUL IN THE COUNTRY Sauter, Eddie, 7/12/1941 (Box 15A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: B159/97A
  - IT'S SWELL OF YOU Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 15A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: A231/704
  - IT'S THE BEAT THAT COUNTS Siravo, George (Box 15A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: B248
  - IT'S THE DREAMER IN ME Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 15A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: A253/22
  - IT'S THE DREAMER IN ME Mundy, Jimmy, 1938 (Box 15A, Folder 16)
    BG No.: A232/21/286
  - IT'S THE MARCH OF THE SWING PARADE Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 15A, Folder 17)
    BG No.: B245
  - IT'S THE TALK OF THE TOWN Lipman, Joe, 11/1961 (Box 15A, Folder 18)
    BG No.: D404/T1
  - IT'S THE TALK OF THE TOWN Powell, Mel, 1/14/1946 (Box 15A, Folder 19)
    BG No.: A128/56/94A
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-2/PGBD
  - IT'S TOO SOON TO KNOW Sauter, Eddie, c.1948 (Box 15B, Folder 20)
    BG No.: A294/113
  - IT'S TOO SOON TO KNOW Hunter, Frank, 10/27/1948 (Box 15B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: A294/125
  - IT'S WONDERFUL Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 15B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: C270/145
  - IT'S YOU I'M TALKING ABOUT Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 15B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: B249/113/50
  - JAM ON THE BREAKS Karlin, Fred, 9/26/1959 (Box 15B, Folder 24)
    BG No.: D67/4
  - JAM SESSION Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 15B, Folder 25)
    BG No.: C237/271
    Parts: saxAAT(-T2)/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
    SaxA1T1 and piano parts are incomplete.
  - JEALOUSY Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 15B, Folder 26)
    BG No.: A110
  - JESS' THEME Sauter, Eddie, 1943 (Box 15C, Folder 27)
    BG No.: 36A/A192
    Parts: cl/saxAATTBBs/tpt1-3/tbn1/PD
  - JINGLE, JANGLE, JINGLE Kirkpatrick, Don, 1942 (Box 15C, Folder 28)